{
    "id": "38aa0ced9fe342348c05c8b71497ee8f",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "................................. is the capital of China.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Beijing",
                "The Beijing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c91cfb31249547969f956bf1f156f363"
        },
        {
            "question": "I first met your Dad at ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Walmart",
                "the Walmart"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7a6f37be5e35474fac27def98017e834"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has failed in ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "English",
                "the English"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "34c1ae924e1d4a40b7fb968662a026c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She died of ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "malaria",
                "the malaria"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8dec9f41ef6247f3a456097da9adb146"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is .......................................... singer I have heard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "best",
                "the best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a28c24b77b2845a8991d959bb6156bc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rose is ........................................ of all flowers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sweetest",
                "the sweetest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "301404fbe1564af28b3ccd629242b804"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................................... is mortal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The man",
                "Man",
                "A man"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7a445727c6f6487bb94a88559487951b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are in .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a trouble",
                "the trouble",
                "trouble"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6451dbe29ed04e4fa09c5e0f6d876fca"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are making ....................................... progress.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a rapid",
                "rapid"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c52b755f2e24ac58f6071506d08d4e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is ..................................... scope for improvement.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a vast",
                "vast",
                "the vast"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d2a3799cf7064995a7285cd3b9fc5df5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your words are not worth ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "penny",
                "a penny"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19f37386fc8146ada44a77638fb7ac8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Donâ€™t make .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noise",
                "a noise"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7617d822f2a4c6a88456490fdfab62e"
        }
    ]
}